Moumen

Hallak

Front-end Developer

I have extensive knowledge of Graphic Short Videos, Social Media Desian. Management, Photography, WordPress, and ReactJS. I am able to combine Web Development and Design in a very pleasing way. I have 8 years of experience in the Media field in general and 5 years of experience in the Web field. Andalus Media Company gave me the opportunity to build over 70 WordPress websites. Additionally, I headed up the company's web department.



Contact





PHONE

+905384770122



EMAIL

me@moumen.net



ADDRESS

Istanbul - Turkey

Hard Skills



Soft Skills



Communication, Problem-solving, Time management, Leadership, Integrity, Teamwork, Creativity.

Languages: Arabic - English - Turkish



www.moumen.net

Education



2020-2024

Bachelor of Computer Science

University of the People

Front-End Web Development Bootcamp

Re:coded

- The Coding Bootcamp took me five months to complete.
- curriculum for Front-end Development.
- I learned HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Redux, Firebase, Git, and Github.
- I developed many responsive projects using these technologies during the Bootcamp.

2021

Front End Development Track

As part of the 1 Million Arab Coders Initiative, I completed the Udacity course for Front-End Development.

Experiences



2017 - Present

Wordpress Developer

Andalus Media

I work as a WordPress developer, responsible for the work progress and finalizing the products to the client.

2018 - Present

Media Consultant

Trust Consultancy

I give consultants and help with finalizing the media products including Graphic Design, and the companny website.

2016 - 2017

Director of Advocacy

Orange Organization

I used to get tasks about creating Humanitarian campaigns, Designing Campaigns, and Social Media Management.

2014 - 2016

Marketing Coordinator

Watan Foundation

I used to get tasks about Graphic Design, Social Media Managment, Photography, and Creating short Videos.





























